JAMELA SANCHEZ

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT

437-566-9511

https://github.com/jamsanch26/myPortfolio.git

897 Brimorton Drive, Scarborough ON, Canada

SKILLS

Programming Languages: C#, CSS, HTML, C++, Java, JavaScript

Frameworks & Libraries: React, Angular, Node.js, Express.js

Tools: GitHub, VS Code, IntelliJ, MySQL, Oracle SQL Developer

Databases: SQL, MongoDB

EDUCATION

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING TECHNICIAN

Centennial College | Canada

College Diploma 2023-2024

BS IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Samar Colleges, Inc. | Philippines Bachelors Degree 2014-2018

REFERENCES

Timothy Cody

Collaborator, Magic Chef Project +1(732) 600-2227, timothybcody@gmail.com

Seyed M. Reza Dibaj

Professor, Centennial College 705-885-5858, rdibaj@my.centennialcollege.ca

Precina Maghari

QA Manager, Nyankids (Cambodia) Ltd. +639978462179, precina.maghari@gmail.com

PROFILE

A Software Engineer with experience and extensive education in software design and application development. A fast learner with great time management, attention to detail, problem solving and multi-tasking skills. Strong work ethic in team or individual settings with excellent communication and interpersonal skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

TEAM MEMBER

September 2023 - November 2023

- Tim Hortons | Scarborough, Ontario
- Entering sales into a cash register and collecting/processing payment.
- · Preparing coffee and food orders.
- Providing great customer service.
- Simple food preparation.

SENIOR QUALITY COORDINATOR

February 2020 - May 2023

- NyanKids (Cambodia) Ltd. | Cambodia
- Booking inspections factory audits and follow-up pre-final inspections.
- Attend PPM, keep and update all necessary documents and quality SOP.
- Responsible for monitoring QA/QC performance by gathering relevant data.
- Performs final inspections, and performance reporting; performs and monitors best practices and training factory staff.

PROJECTS

THE MAGIC CHEF

June 2024 - August 2024

- O Centennial College | Canada
- The Magic Chef is a web application developed using React.js, Express.js, Node.js, and
 MongoDB. It offers a diversecollection of recipes customized to users' tastes and dietary
 needs. Users can rate and review recipes, receivepersonalized recommendations based on
 their preferences, easily navigate through the app, and engage with acommunity of fellow
 food enthusiasts.
- You can refer to repo at https://github.com/jamsanch26/WebAppProject.git

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS

Y ON-JOB-TRAINING MONITORING SYSTEM Samar Colleges, Inc. | Philippines

- Won the 2018 Best Capstone Project Design and System Operation
- Well-Crafted Manuscript Project Design and System Operation
- Best Presentor Capstone Project Design and System Operation